# Rafuat Aazmi Khan 🕡 Featured

Senior System Engineer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Requirement Gathering, System Analysis, Technical Architecture, Project Management, Client Management, Linux, Devops, Python, SQL, PL/SQL, Azure Fundamentals



Current Designation: Senior System Engineer Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 1 Month(s)

Current Company: Infosys

Notice Period: Currently Serving Notice Period

Current Location: Pune

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Delhi / NCR, Pune Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Senior System Engineer, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Requirement Gathering, System Analysis, Technical Architecture, Project Management, Client Management, Linux, Devops, Python,

PLSQL, Azure Fundamentals

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

### **Summary**

I am a BE graduate currently working as a Senior System Engineer in Infosys. I have an experience of 3 years in Financial Crime and Anti Money Laundering Domain. I have worked on BAE designed tools like Detica and NetReveal. Currently I am engaged in designing the solution for customer risk assessment model which classify and assign the calculated risk to the onboarded customers. I have a good knowledge on various Banking processes like Customer Risk Assessment, Customer/Payment Screening and Compliance reporting. I have also worked in the Support and Maintenance team where I managed multiple P1/P2 incidents including live issues on day to day basis. I was also recognized for successfully migrating the manual deployment process to Devops framework.

# **Work Experience**

Infosys Limited as Senior System Engineer

Dec 2017 to Dec 2017

Project Title: Financial Crime System (DETICA and NetReveal Application)

Client: One of the leading Bank in Australia.

Role Description: Support Analyst in Support and Maintenance team

Role and Responsibilities:

Resolved high priority issue to keep the application available 24X7.

Experience in P1/P2 issue fixes and meeting all the SLA's.

Implementation of multiple infrastructure changes.

Creation and Resolution of PBI's and PKE's

Identified major fallback in current design and implemented enhancement. Done multiple successful deployment using Devops tools like Jenkins, CARA

#### Infosys

Dec 2017 to Dec 2017

#### Infosys

Dec 2017 to Dec 2017

Infosys as Senior System Engineer Dec 2017 to Till Date

Senior Systems Engineer working on data analysis and designing solutions for financial crime domain. Familiar with working on python and sql.

#### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Institute for Technology and Management (ITM) GWALIOR in 2017

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

AZ-900

Infosys Global Agile Developer

### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
PL/SQL, Linux, Websphere	
Control-M, Devops, Python	
Azure Fundamentals	

### Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
english				

## **Projects**

Project Title: Financial Crime System

Client: Westpac Bank

Duration: Jun 2018 - Jan 2021 Nature of Employment: Full Time Onsite / Offsite: Onsite

Project Details: Worked on financial crime domain

### **Affirmative Action**

### **Work Authorization**

Category: General Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time